How many more days do you think
his life can burn for this world?
But that friend of yours is really smart.
He knew he couldn't escape,
so he wanted to use his last breath
to protect you and everyone else
so you could get out.
Inside this is the system backdoor key
he forcibly extracted
using administrator privileges.
He asked me to pass it to you.
He wants you to destroy this fake world
and bring everyone back to reality.
What about him?
If the system shatters,
how will he get out?
Get out?
From the moment he got this USB drive,
he never planned
to leave himself a way out.
No,
I will absolutely not
leave him behind alone.
I'm going to take him out alive with me.
You two are exactly the same,
both valuing the other's life
more than your own.
Listen,
the Shepherd is not invincible.
His algorithm is absolutely rational
and can automatically repair
anger or fear.
But there is one thing
he cannot calculate:
the emotional paradox.
Emotional paradox?
What does that mean?
Machines can never calculate
the contradiction of true human emotions.
When someone is in soul-tearing pain
but can still smile gently.
This kind of relief in pain
is a virus
that can crash the system instantly.
But this kind of data,
ordinary people
cannot generate.
Only the current Liu Yiyang
can generate it.
Xiao Han,
you must make him smile
at his most painful moment.
smile.
The core server
is underground in that building
in the city center.
Only the current administrator can enter.
Southwest.
You must make him smile
at his most painful moment.
smile.
I'm sorry, Liu Yiyang.
For you to live,
I have to be the bad guy.
Han,
how exactly do we create this emotional
paradox Shen Lan mentioned?
create?
Can't we just tell Yang directly
and ask him to cooperate and smile?
No,
the Shepherd is monitoring
Liu Yiyang's data at all times.
If there is even a hint of acting,
the system will recognize it immediately.
That way,
not only will we fail to save him,
but we'll also doom him.
Then what should we do?
Only real pain can fool the system.
At the most critical moment,
I will tell him myself
that I've been using him from the start,
and now he's useless.
Are you crazy?
Yang is almost dying to protect us.
dying.
If you stab him in the heart now,
he won't be able to hold on.
If I don't stab him,
he'll die.
Only by making him think I betrayed him,
plunging him into
the deepest abyss of pain,
will his smile
destroy this system.
But what about you?
Are you really going to destroy
all the trust between you two
with your own hands
and make him hate you forever?
As long as I can get him out alive,
he can hate me all he wants.
Once the gate opens,
if he wants to kill me,
I'll pay him with my life.
Dr. Xiao,
how come you have time for a stroll today?
I felt suffocated,
so I came out for some fresh air.
Qiqi isn't feeling well.
I'm afraid we can't go to the park
outside the city.
Is that so?
What a pity.
Alert: Target
Xiao Han has made contact
with Xiaopang and Qiqi.
Abnormal emotional fluctuation detected.
Administrator,
please handle it immediately.
It's a shame to waste such good weather.
Xiao Han,
you know everything.
Do I?
I do.
You're turning to ash faster and faster.
It means this instance
is about to collapse.
We must go to the core building
before the world resets.
You really
have no sympathy at all.
I'm almost turning into a monster,
and you won't even comfort me.
Shen Lan gave this to me.
But he said only you have access
to the core building.
Take me in tonight.
Shen Lan is quite efficient.
Good job.
Once the access is unlocked tonight,
you'll have served your final purpose.
Meet me at the gate tonight.
Don't be late.
Warning: Multiple unauthorized
lifeforms detected
entering the core area.
Initiating physical elimination protocol.
Han, Yang can't hold on much longer!
Hurry and use Shen Lan's USB drive
to stop the system!
No, the USB drive can only be used
on the core server.
If we use it now,
all our efforts will be in vain.
Liu Yiyang, keep pushing forward!
Don't stop!
Get into the secret room.
You guys wait for us outside.
...
Detachment protocol initiated.
Forcing reset of administrator data.
Hurry and plug in the USB drive!
Xiao Han, plug in the USB drive!
Destroy it! As long as the system
is destroyed,
you can...
Stop moving yourself to tears.
Do you think you're saving everyone?
Xiao Han, what are you talking about?
I've known all along that
the only core access to this system
is on you.
If I didn't play the part of your
life-and-death comrade all the way,
how could you willingly risk your life
to open the door for me?
Now the act is over,
and your value has come to an end.
An act?
So everything along the way
was just an act?
Yes.
I thought at least the bond between us
was real.
At least I could get a thank you from you.
That's not friendship.
That's self-satisfaction.
From the very beginning,
my only goal was
to get out alive.
As for whether you live or die,
it has nothing to do with me.
Warning.
Administrator Liu Yiyang's
mental breakdown is at 99%.
Extreme anger, sorrow,
and despair data detected.
The system is accelerating
the recovery of permissions.
So that's how it is.
But it's good if it means
you guys can go back.
Anyway, just like you said,
I'm just a self-righteous saint.
Xiao Han,
you must live on.
Then I wish you a safe journey.
Warning.
Unresolvable contradictory
emotional data detected.
Algorithm logic is caught
in an infinite loop.
Unable to calculate.
Unable to repair.
System overload.
Liu Yiyang.
The core is collapsing.
Liu Yiyang,
Liu Yiyang, don't close your eyes.
We agreed to leave together.
We have to get out together.
I was lying to you just now.
I was lying.
Xiao Han,
why?
I'm sorry, Liu Yiyang. I'm sorry.
If I didn't do this,
none of us would be able to leave.
How could I leave you behind?
I will never leave you alone.
We have to get out of here alive together.
I'll take you home.
Damn you.
You acted so well.
When we get back,
this won't be over
without ten big meals.
Okay, whatever you want to eat
when we get back, it's on me.
Hang in there.
Han, Yang,
you're both okay.
Great, the plan worked.
We can go back.
Underlying logic rewrite detected.
Administrator permissions
have been revoked.
The world will return to reality.
Let's go.
Congratulations, players.
You have successfully cleared
the fifth station, Perfect Reality.
The return channel will soon open
for you to return to true reality.
Congratulations, players,
on passing the qualifiers.
Welcome, players,
to the official tournament.
Game rule: Only one car
can survive between cars.